Guide to the William R. and Louise Fielder Sheet Music Collection
Department of Special Collections
William R. and Louise Fielder Sheet Music Collection
Special Collections M701
Fielder, William R. Fielder, Louise
44 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions:
None.
Provenance:
Purchased from William R. and Louise Fielder
SCOPE AND CONTENT
The Fielder Sheet Music Collection represents the fruit of the collecting labors of William R. and Louise Fielder. The collection consists of 2,532 individual pieces of sheet music, sheet music lithographs, and music related broadsides from the United States in the 19th and early 20th centuries. Accompanying the sheet music are eighty files of correspondence, ephemera, and photocopies of the collection. In all, the collection is arranged into forty-two distinct series. Every effort has been made to preserve the provenance of the collection's series which Mr. and Mrs. Fielder utilized during their years of collecting.
The forty-two series are arranged by subject, by lithographic images, by geographical region, and by the era of origin. Within the individual series, no effort has been made to sequentially arrange the individual pieces. None of the series is exhaustive of its subject matter; nor are the series titles necessarily perfectly representative of the contents of the series. The best guide to the collection is the individual record found in the finding aid itself.
The collection's strengths lie in several areas. Among these are the collections of imprints dating before 1840, the 19th century imprints from the Northeast United States, and the mid-19th century imprints from California and Hawaii. Of particular note in this collection are the imprints of war-related themes, which scan American history from the arrival of General LaFayette, to Confederate imprints printed during the Civil War and continuing through the first and second World Wars. Of equal importance is the representation of daily life in the19th century and the extensive collection of early-American lithography which this collection contains.
The finding aid for the Fielder Sheet Music Collection essays to document all available information about the individual pieces of sheet music. To enable the researcher easier access to the collection, the finding aid can be searched by title, composer, arranger, performer, lithographer, by city of origin and publishing house, as well as by date of origin.
SERIES DESCRIPTION
- Series 1. Albums
- Series 2. Animals
- Series 3. Automobiles and Airplanes
- Series 4. Irving Berlin
- Series 5. Blacks and Minstrels
- Series 6. California
  - Subseries a. Illustrated with original photographs
  - Subseries b. 1836 - 1849, Westward Ho
  - Subseries c. 1870 - 1879, Non-Illustrated
  - Subseries d. 1880 - 1889
  - Subseries e. 1890 - 1899
  - Subseries f. 20th Century
- Series 7. California and Hawaii
  - Subseries a. 1850 - 1859
  - Subseries b. 1860 - 1869
  - Subseries c. 1870 - 1879, Illustrated
- Series 8. George M. Cohan
- Series 9. Comic
- Series 10. Dancing
- Series 11. Drinking
- Series 12. Famous Composers and Operas, 19th Century
- Series 13. Famous People, 19th Century
- Series 14. Fashion
- Series 15. Fires
- Series 16. Flowers
- Series 17. Stephen Collins Foster First Editions
- Series 18. L. M. Gottschalk
- Series 19. Indians
- Series 20. Irish and Will Hays
- Series 21. Al Jolson
- Series 22. Lithographers and Artists
- Series 23. Love, Childhood, Home
- Series 24. Military, 19th Century
  - Subseries a. Confederate Imprints
  - Subseries b. General
  - Subseries c. General Lafayette
- Series 25. E. T. Paull
- Series 26. Places, Events, Things
- Series 27. Political, 1840 - 1843
- Series 28. Prefire Chicago
- Series 29. Rags
- Series 30. Ships
- Series 31. Special Items
  - Subseries a. 19th Century
  - Subseries b. 20th Century
- Series 32. Sports
- Series 33. Transportation
- Series 34. Uncle Tom's Cabin and Little Eva
- Series 35. William Vincent Wallace
- Series 36. Women
- Series 37. Pre-1840 Imprints
- Series 38. 19th Century Imprints
- Series 39. 20th Century Imprints
- Series 40. Oversize
- Series 41. William R. and Louise Fielder Ephemera
- Series 42. Photocopies
CONTAINER LIST
- Series 1. Albums
  - Music / [collected by] Florine Haas (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Whisper your mother's name / words by Harry Braisted, music by Stanley Carter --Mamie Reilly: waltz song and chorus / written and composed by Maude Nugent --A hot time in the old town / words by Joe Hayden, written by Theo A. Metz --My coal black lady: symphony de Ethiopia / written and composed by W. T. Jefferson --There may be others like her but the're not in town: a beautiful ballad with waltz refrain / words by Cha[rle]s Horwitz, music by Fred[eric]k Bowers --King Carnival march (two-step) / by George Rosey --Ma Caroline: a refine coon song / words and music by Lee Johnson --Wang: potpourri / libretto by J. Cheever Goodwin, music by Woolson Morse --The sporty widow Brown / words by Harry Braisted, music by Stanley Carter --Bye bye Belinda: a darktown triumph / written and composed by H. Y. Leavitt --I was once your wife! / words by Raymond A. Browne, music by Monroe H. Rosenfeld --Sweet Rosie O'Grady: waltz song and chorus / written and composed by Maude Nugent --I want yer, ma honey: an Ethiopian oddity / words and music by Fay Templeton --She's the comfort of their home / written and composed by Ed. Rogers --Doris the village maiden / words and music by Geo. Maywood --Love's dream after the ball (Songe d'amour apres le bal) / by A. Czibulka --Espanita: Spanish waltzes / composed by George Rosey --El Capitan march / by John Philip Sousa --King Cotton march / by John Philip Sousa --Since my little baby brother came to stay: a serio-comic novelty / written and composed by Gertrude R. Spellan
    Harry Braisted; Stanley Carter; Maude Nugent; Joe Hayden; Theo A. Metz; W. T. Jefferson; Charles Horwitz; Frederick Bowers; George Rosey; Lee Johnson; J. Cheever Goodwin; Woolson Morse; Stanley Carter; H. Y. Leavitt; Raymond A. Browne; Monroe H. Rosenfeld; Fay Templeton; Ed. Rogers; Geo. Maywood; A. Czibulka; George Rosey; John Philip Sousa; Gertrude R. Spellan
  - Marches / [collected by] B. L. W. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Hail to the spirit of liberty march / by John Philip Sousa --A little bit of fun (San toy): two-step / arranged by M. C. Brown, melodies by Lionel Monckton --Parson Johnson's rag-time mule: a characteristic two step, march or cake-walk / by Edgar E. Huston --The rag time sports: cake walk, march, and two-step / by James Haack --The Honolulu cake walk: a characteristic march / composed by J. W. Lerman --Queen of the ragtime: a syncopated two step / by Harry Powers --Darktown parade march comique / composed by J. Henri Fischer --The surprise Turkish midnight parade / by Maurice Akst --Ragged William march and two step (with apologies to Rossini) / by Frank P. Banta --The purple lady: march and two-step / by Burt Lesser --Smoky Mokes: cakewalk and two-step / composed by A. Holzmann / Ma rag time baby: two step for piano / by Fred S. Stone --The Honolulu cake walk ragtime march / composed by J. W. Lerman --Rag-time intermezzo: a syncopated symphony / by Maxwell Silver --Fiddle-dee-dee: march and two-step / lyrics by Edgar Smith, music by John Stromberg / Policy Sam: cake walk and two step / by Joseph Gioscia --A warm reception: characteristic march, two-step and cake-walk / by Bert R. Anthony --The rounders: a Vaudeville in three acts / lyrics by Harry B. Smith, music by Ludwig Englander --March from the comic opera 'The singing girl' / arranged by F. W. Meacham, book by Stanislaus Stange, lyrics by Harry B. Smith, music by Victor Herbert --Primrose march and cake-walk / by Carl Carlton --Ching Ling Foo: Chinese rag time march and two step / by Emil Katzenstein --March from the comic opera 'The Ameer' / book by Frederic Ranken and Kirke La Shelle, music by Victor Herbert, arranged by F. W. Meacham --The man behind the gun: march from 'Chris and the wonderful lanp' / by John Philip Sousa --De watermelon brigade: charactersitic march-two step / by J. W. Wheeler --Young and dashing: march and two-step / by Rudolph Aronson --In command: march and two step / by J. Ben Michaelis --John Philip Sousa march: two-step / composed by Ernst Bial --March from the comic opera 'Cyrano de Bergerac' / lyrics by Harry B. Smith, music by Victor Herbert, arranged by F. W. Meacham --The electric wave march / by O. E. Sutton --Miss Jollity: march and two-step / composed by Thomas Chilvers --The Creole queen: characteristic march (two step) / by R. B. Hall --Olympic two step, dedicated to the Olympic Gun Club of San Francisco, Cal. / by C. F. Stone --The mosquitoes' parade: a Jersey review / by Howard Whitney --The Mississippi side-step: characteristic march and cake walk (in simplified rag-time / composed by Leo E. Berliner --Bunch o'blackberries: cake-walk and two-step / composed by Abe Holzmann --Foolish William: characteristic two-step / by Thurland Chattaway
    Thurland Chattaway; John Philip Sousa; M. C. Brown; Lionel Monckton; Edgar E. Huston; James Haack; J. W. Lerman; Harry Powers; J. Henri Fischer; Maurice Akst; Frank P. Banta; Burt Lesser; A. Holzmann; Fred S. Stone; Maxwell Silver; Edgar Smith; John Stromberg; Joseph Gioscia; Bert R. Anthony; Harry B. Smith; Ludwig Englander; F. W. Meacham; Victor Herbert; Carl Carlton; Emil Katzenstein; Frederic Ranken; Kirke La Shelle; Rudolph Aronson; J. Ben Michaelis; Ernst Bial; O. E. Sutton; Thomas Chilvers; R. B. Hall; C. F. Stone; Howard Whitney; Leo E. Berliner; Abe Holzmann; Thurland Chattaway
  - Marches / [collected by] B. L. W. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Dixieland, introducing Old Black Joe: march and two-step / composed by Chauncey Haines --The mosquitoes' parade: a Jersey review / by Howard Whitney --Our director: march / by F. E. Bigelow --The tale of the sea shell: march and two-step from 'the Prince of Pilsen' / lyrics by Frank Pixley, music by Gustav Luders --March from Ade and Wathall's musical comedy 'The Sultan of Sulu' / lyrics by George Ade, music by Alfred G. Wathall, arranged by Hilding Anderson --Harlem rag: two-step / arranged by D. S. De Lisle, composed by Tom Turpin --The rabbit's promenade: two-step for piano / by G. H. Wilder --Just ask me: ragtime march and two-step / by Charles Hunter --A pickanniny christening: characteristic march / by Winthrop Wiley --Anona: intermezzo two step / by Vivian Grey --The bogie man: character march and two-step / by Charles A. Carvel --A warm reception: characteristic march, two-step and cake-walk / by Bert R. Anthony --Iris: a Greek intermezzo / by Ellis R. Ephraim --Les soldats qui passent: marche / by P. Mario Costa --A lucky duck: a webfoot promenade / by Howard Whitney --The Mississippi bubble: march two-step / by Chauncey Haines --Hunky-dory: cake-walk and two step / composed by Abe Holzmann --Ma gum-elastic girl: a cake walk march and two-step / by H. Y. Leavitt --The donkey laugh: 'a musical horseonyou' / by Howard Whitney --Dixie girl: characteristic march two step / composed by J. Bodewalt Lampe --Checkers: characteristic march two-step / by N. M. Stokes --Fame and fortune: march and two step / Chas. J. Rockwell --College girls: march and two step / composed by C. A. Grimm --Possum and taters: a ragtime feast / composed by Charles Hunter --Lickity-split: two step & march / by C. J. Penny --Fine and dandy: march and two step / by W[illia]m Frederick Peters --Sunrise in Georgia: march -two step / by Sheppard Camp --Princess Pocahontas: march and two-step / text by Al Trahern, composed by Richmond F. Hoyt, arranged by Hugo O. Marks --Frocks and frills march: two-step / by Raymond Dixy --Dreamy eyes: characteristic march and two step / composed by J. Bodewalt Lampe --Cotton bolls: two step / by Cha[rle]s Hunter --Hurrah boys!: march and two step / composed by Joseph Lacalle --The assembly: march and two-step / by Paul Eno --Frog puddles / by Howard Whitney --Don't make dem scandalous eyes at me: march or two step / Lee Johnson
    Chauncey Haines; Howard Whitney; F. E. Bigelow; Frank Pixley; Gustav Luders; George Ade; Alfred G. Wathall; Hilding Anderson; D. S. De Lisle; Tom Turpin; G. H. Wilder; Charles Hunter; Winthrop Wiley; Vivian Grey; Mabel McKinley; Charles A. Carvel; Bert R. Anthony; Ellis R. Ephraim; P. Mario Costa; Howard Whitney; Abe Holzmann; H. Y. Leavitt; J. Bodewalt Lampe; N. M. Stokes; Chas. J. Rockwell; C. A. Grimm; Charles Hunter; C. J. Penny; William Frederick Peters; Sheppard Camp; Al Trahern; Richmond F. Hoyt; Hugo O. Marks; Raymond Dixy; Joseph Lacalle; Paul Eno; Lee Johnson
  - Music (Box 2, Folder 2)
    I guess I'll have to telegraph my baby: coon song / words and music by Geo[rge] M. Cohan --My love's a gamblin' man (if you'll only stop dat shootin' craps): song and chorus with dance ad lib / words by Matthews and Bulger, music by Maurice Levi --Ma onliest one! / words and music by Fay Templeton --The lilac / words by Marion May and Gustave H. Kline, music by Gustave H. Kline --I've been to gay Paree / words by Tom Conley and Henry J. Sayers, music by Felix McGlennon --Honey, you made a hit with me! / words and music by Ernest Hogan and Bert A. Williams --La pas ma la / words and music by Ernest Hogan --Der'll be wahm coons a prancin' / words by Paul Laurence Dunbar, music by Will Marion --Ma hoodoo honey / words by Al Anderson, music by Lee Johnson --She was bred in old Kentucky / words by Harry Braisted, music by Stanley Carter --I love my honey, yes I do! / words and music by William C. Carleton --Oh! Ebenezer! / words and music by Dave Reed, Jr. --Elsie from Chelsea / words and music by Harry Dacre --I've sold my cow (Jack and choruses): from 'The strange adventures of Jack and the beanstalk' / words by R. A. Barnett, music by A. B. Sloane --You're so good, Daddy: song and chorus / words and music by Hattie Starr --Chimmie Fadden der Bowery boy: song and chorus / words and music by Charles H. Hopper --All I wants is ma chickens / arranged by W. H. Tyers, words and music by Deas and Wilson --Crappy Dan de spo'tin' man / words and music by Charles E. Trevathan --I've been hoodoo'd: comic song and refrain / words and music by Gussie L. Davis --Because: song and chorus / words by Cha[rle]s Horwitz, music by Fred[eric]k V. Bowers --How'd you like to be the iceman?: song and chorus / words and music by Helf and Moran --Honey does you love yer man?: a coon love song / words by Walter H. Ford, music by John W. Bratton --Naughty red riding hood / words and music by Geo[rge] R. Brill, arranged by Carlton S. Moore --
    George M. Cohan; Matthews and Bulger; Maurice Levi; Fay Templeton; Marion May; Gustave H. Kline; Tom Conley; Henry J. Sayers; Felix McGlennon; Ernest Hogan; Bert A. Williams; Paul Laurence Dunbar; Will Marion; Al Anderson; Lee Johnson; Harry Braisted; Stanley Carter; William C. Carleton; Dave Reed, Jr.; Harry Dacre; R. A. Barnett; A. B. Sloane; Hattie Starr; Charles H. Hopper; W. H. Tyers; Deas and Wilson; Charles E. Trevathan; Gussie L. Davis; Charles Horwitz; Frederick V. Bowers; Helf and Moran; Walter H. Ford; John W. Bratton; George R. Brill; Carlton S. Moore
  - Music: [San Francisco] Examiner Supplement Songs (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Honey you're the warmest gal in town / words and music by Irving Jones --The tattooed man: Abel and chorus / by Frank Daniels --Golden poppy two-step / written by Edward Galz --I don't know how to tell yer how I lubs yer: Marie Lloyd's English coon song / words and music by Bennett Scott --When the parson makes Miss Mandy Johnson mine / words by Dan Packard, music by Robert Cone --I'll carve dat nigger when we meet / by Walter Hawley, arranged by D. S. de Lisle --I love ma honey best of all / words and music by Ernest Hogan, arranged by J. A. Raynes --Just about to fall / words by Cy Warman, music by Raymon Moore --Come, ye lofty! Come, ye lowly!: Christmas carol / music by George William Warren --A tar at a masquerade / words by Robert H. Davis, music by C. von Gerichten --Honey you've done me wrong / words and music by Harold M. Vernon --That sad sweet word good bye / words by Louis Weslyn Jones, music by Carl Vandal --When someone pulls the string / words and music by Charles Hoyt --May Irwin's 'bully' song / words and music by Charles E. Trevathan --I'll carve dat nigger when we meet / by Walter Hawley, arranged by D. S. de Lisle --Nigger, nigger, newver die: a coon simplicity / words by W[illia]m Osborn, music by Nellie Sylvester --In dreamland / words by Harry B. Smith, music by Victor Herbert --Sweetheart the time will come / words by Charles Shackford, music by Kerry Mills --On the road to Mandalay: a barrack-room ballad / words by Rudyard Kipling, music revised and adapted by Henry Trevannion --When the little ones are coming home from school / words by Howard Graham, music by Charles Graham --Secrets they whispered in May: descriptive / words by W. R. Black, music by Code Morgan --O holy night: Christmas song / arranged by Ja[me]s J. Freeman --Life's game of see-saw / words by Edgar Selden, music by L. C. Wedgefuth --A merry man and a merry maid: a carol / words by H. V. Southerland, music by H. M. Bosworth --I've been faithful to you / words and music by Cha[rle]s K. Harris, arranged by Joseph Clauder --Lucy! Tell me I'm your beau / by Safford Waters --She is my picnic girl / words and music by Harry Connor --Klondike gold / words by R. S. Phelps, music by Leo Bruck --Sweet Katy Carney, my lass from Killarney / words by Harry J. Cox, music by Jos[eph] B. Carey
    Irving Jones; Frank Daniels; Edward Galz; Bennett Scott; Dan Packard; Robert Cone; Walter Hawley; D. S. de Lisle; Ernest Hogan; J. A. Raynes; Cy Warman; Raymon Moore; George William Warren; Robert H. Davis; C. von Gerichten; Harold M. Vernon; Louis Weslyn Jones; Carl Vandal; Charles Hoyt; Charles E. Trevathan; William Osborn; Nellie Sylvester; Harry B. Smith; Victor Herbert; Charles Shackford; Kerry Mills; Rudyard Kipling; Henry Trevannion; Howard Graham; Charles Graham; W. R. Black; Code Morgan; James J. Freeman; Edgar Selden; L. C. Wedgefuth; H. V. Southerland; H. M. Bosworth; Charles K. Harris; Joseph Clauder; Safford Waters; Harry Connor; R. S. Phelps; Leo Bruck; Harry J. Cox; Joseph B. Carey
  - Music / [collected by] Ed. Brandenstein (Box 3, Folder 2)
    The girl I love, loves me / words and music by Gussie L. Davis --Put me off at Buffalo: comic song and refrain / words by Harry Dillon, music by John Dillon --And her golden hair was hanging down her back / written and composed by Felix McGlennon and Monroe H. Rosenfeld --Only one girl in the world for me: song and chorus / words and music by Dave Marion --He stole McCarthy's wife / words by Thomas Le Mack, music by Andrew Mack --Mamie! Come kiss your honey boy / words and music by May Irwin --My Pearl's a Bowery girl! / words by W[illia]m Jerome, music by Andrew Mack --The streets of Cairo, or The poor little country maid / arranged by G. M. Rosenberg, written and composed by James Thornton --Say 'au revoir' but not 'good-bye' / words and music by Harry Kennedy --The sidewalks of New York: song and chorus / arranged by Cha[rle]s Miller, words and music by Cha[rle]s B. Lawlor and James W. Blake --What right has he on Broadway?: march song and chorus / words by Harry Dillon, music by Nat Mann --Standing on the corner, didn't mean no harm, or, Oh, my baby, tell me true / by Geo[rge] Evans --She was a daisy: song / words by J. Cheever Goodwin, music by W[illia]m Furst --Knights of the mystic star: song / words by Edward Harrigan, music by Dave Braham --Molly O / written and composed by W[illia]m J. Scanlan --Daisy Bell / written and composed by Harry Dacre --It's English as you see it on Broadway / words and music by Cha[rle]s H. Hoyt --Oh! Uncle John: comic song / words and music by Felix McGlennon --Darling Mabel / arranged by Frederic Schneider, words and music by W. P. Chase --Still his whiskers grew / words by Albert Hall, music by C. W. Murphy --Ma Jeanette / written by Richard Norton, composed by Sidney Jones --The man that broke the bank at Monte Carlo / written and composed by Fred. Gilbert --Love in springtime (Se saran rose) / English poetry by Nathan Haskell Dole, Italian poetry by Pietro Mazzoni, music by Luigi Arditi --Put me off at Buffalo: comic song and refrain / words by Harry Dillon, music by John Dillon --Louisiana Lou / written and composed by Leslie Stuart --A pretty girl, a summer night / words by J. Cheever Goodwin, music by Woolson Morse --Isabella: song from '1492' / words by R. A. Barnet, music by Carl Pflueger --Sweet Marie / words by Cy Warman, music by Raymon Moore --Honey, O!: an Ethiopian comic song / words and music by Percy Gaunt --Everybody takes his hat off to me / words and music by Barney Fagan --I long to see the girl I left behind / written and composed by John T. Kelly --Ben Bolt: Oh! Don't you remember sweet Alice? / words by Tho[ma]s Dunn English, music by Nelson Kneass --Wont you come to my tea-party / arranged by Jno. T. Hall, words and music by Alb[ert] H. Fitz --My best girl's a New Yorker / written and composed by John Stromberg --The band played on / words by John F. Palmer, music by Charles B. Ward --Hush yo' business, oh, go on!: a coon warning / words by Sager Midgley, music by Maurice Levi --I want yer ma honey: an Ethiopian oddity / words and music by Fay Templeton --Celeste / words by Arthur Macy, music by Edgar A. P. Newcomb --What could the poor girl do?: comic song / words and music by E. Alexandria --Lucinda-Cinda-Jane: a sable serenade / words and music by Joseph Hart --I'm gwine to marry Missa Truscalina Brown: a Senegambian romanza / arranged by Henry S. Sawyer, words and music by Ja[me]s E. Sullivan --Keep those golden gates wide open: song and chorus / words and music by Joesph Hart --Kitty (the Bowery boy to his sweetheart) / words by Joseph Flynn, music by Andrew Mack --Henrietta! Have you met her? / words by Walter H. Ford, music by J. W. Bratton --Mud-pie days / arranged by Jos[eph] Clauder, words and music by Charles K. Harris --Wont you be my sweetheart: waltz song and refrain / words by J. G. Judson, music by H. C. Verner --Private Tommy Atkins: song / words by Henry Hamilton, music by S. Potter --Margery! / written and composed by Arthur West --I can't change it: a humorour ditty / words and music by T. W. Connor
    Gussie L. Davis; Harry Dillon; John Dillon; Felix McGlennon; Monroe H. Rosenfeld; Dave Marion; Thomas Le Mack; Andrew Mack; May Irwin; William Jerome; G. M. Rosenberg; James Thornton; Harry Kennedy; Charles Miller; Charles B. Lawlor; James W. Blake; Harry Dillon; Nat Mann; George Evans; J. Cheever Goodwin; William Furst; Edward Harrigan; Dave Braham; William J. Scanlan; Harry Dacre; Charles H. Hoyt; Felix McGlennon; Frederic Schneider; W. P. Chase; Albert Hall; C. W. Murphy; Richard Norton; Sidney Jones; Fred. Gilbert; Nathan Haskell Dole; Pietro Mazzoni; Luigi Arditi; Leslie Stuart; Woolson Morse; R. A. Barnet; Carl Pflueger; Raymon Moore; Cy Warman; Percy Gaunt; Barney Fagan; John T. Kelly; Thomas Dunn English; Nelson Kneass; J. T. Hall; Albert H. Fitz; John Stromberg; John F. Palmer; Charles B. Ward; Sager Midgley; Maurice Levi; Fay Templeton; Arthur Macy; Edgar A. P. Newcomb; E. Alexandria; Joseph Hart; Henry S. Sawyer; James E. Sullivan; Joesph Hart; Joseph Flynn; Walter H. Ford; J. W. Bratton; Joseph Clauder; Charles K. Harris; J. G. Judson; H. C. Verner; Henry Hamilton; S. Potter; Arthur West; T. W. Connor
  - Music - Vocal (Box 4, Folder 1)